funny-city.com 2006-06-27

# Adtegrity.com Internet Advertising Solutions - Privacy Policy

|   
---  
  |  |   |  **_Home_**  >  Privacy Policy  
---|---  
  
|   | Privacy Policy  
---|---  
  |  Adtegrity.com observes the following privacy policy in our commitment to assuring privacy for publishers, advertisers, and Web site visitors.  
| **Collected Information**  
  |  Adtegrity.com, through sign-up and application processes, collects publisher and advertiser personal information, which is used solely for billing, payout and marketing purposes.  
  |  |  | Publisher Information: name, email address, phone number, site URL, and monthly impressions.  
---|---  
|  Advertiser Information: name, title, company name, address, country of residence, phone number, fax number and email address.  
| **Non-Disclosure**  
  |  Adtegrity.com is committed to protecting the privacy of our publishers, advertisers, and Web site visitors. Adtegrity.com does not disclose any of the gathered information to third parties. While Adtegrity.com cannot fully control the actions of their Web site publishers, Adtegrity.com does require full disclosure of each site's privacy guidelines for every site that serves Adtegrity.com ads.  
| **Information Use**  
  |  If Adtegrity.com, Inc, for any reason uses the personal information that publishers/advertisers have provided, written permission will be obtained before doing so. The only exception to this will be the use of a publisher's company name and/or logo while finding advertising to be used on their site, or to promote the Adtegrity.com network.  
| **Cookies**  
  |  If a visitor to a Web site views an ad served by Adtegrity.com, they are assigned a unique number, known as a cookie, that is recorded and stored on their computer in their Web browser's cookie file. If the visitor then visits another Web site that has ads served by Adtegrity.com, the cookie is recognized by the computer and may be used to target ads to that Web surfer based on his or her past browsing experience. Cookies do not harm visitors' computers and do not gather personal information.  
| **Why Use Cookies?**  
  |   
  |  Overall, the cookie helps the ad network, Adtegrity.com, determine which advertisements best fit which visitors and which Web sites. A visitor may choose to opt-out on using cookies at any time by following a simple procedure to manually delete them. Visitors should refer to their respective browser's user manual for instructions.  
| **Third Party Advertising**  
  |  The ads appearing on this Web site are delivered to you by third-party advertisers, our Web advertising partners. Information about your visit to this site, such as number of times you have viewed an ad (but not your name, address, or other personal information), is used to serve ads to you on this site. For more information about third-party advertisers, cookies, and how to "opt-out", please visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp>.  
| **Third Party Cookies**  
  |  In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser.
